<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>article on Salomon Marquez</title>
    <link>https://sblaizerwize.github.io/categories/article/</link>
    <description>Recent content in article on Salomon Marquez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sblaizerwize.github.io/categories/article/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Simple Guide to use ChatGPT via the OpenAI API</title>
      <link>https://sblaizerwize.github.io/posts/use-chatgpt-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sblaizerwize.github.io/posts/use-chatgpt-with-python/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT is a state-of-the-art language model developed by OpenAI. It serves many purposes in natural language processing, including language translation, chatbots, and story writing, among others.
This guide describes how to utilize ChatGPT through the OpenAI API service on macOS operating systems. Additionally, it provides instructions for interacting with ChatGPT using Python.
 Connect to ChatGPT via API To set up ChatGPT API follow these instructions:
 Set up an API Key Sign up to OpenAI and follow the indications to create a new secret key.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secret Ingredients Found in Kaggle Competitions from 2021 to 2023</title>
      <link>https://sblaizerwize.github.io/posts/top5-kaggle-competitions-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sblaizerwize.github.io/posts/top5-kaggle-competitions-2023/</guid>
      <description>In May 2023, Kaggle launched the AI Report competition. The aim was to summarize what the ML community has learned about working and experimenting with AI over the past two years. The competition considered seven pivotal categories: text data, image and video data, tabular and time series data, Kaggle competitions, Generative AI, ethics, and others. Overall, 220 teams and 279 competitors submitted their reports, and a panel of seven Kaggle Grandmasters reviewed them to select the best of them in each category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Dictionaries</title>
      <link>https://sblaizerwize.github.io/posts/fundamentalsofdictionaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sblaizerwize.github.io/posts/fundamentalsofdictionaries/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in learning about a more efficient way to store and access information than using a traditional list? Consider using dictionaries. A dictionary, also known as an associative array, map, hash, or hash map, is a data structure that represents objects as key-value pairs, making it easy to access information by knowing a key.
For instance, suppose you want to create an inventory of your video games, including information like name, genre, platforms, and ratings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Airbyte on a Microsoft Azure VM</title>
      <link>https://sblaizerwize.github.io/posts/airbyte-azure-vm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sblaizerwize.github.io/posts/airbyte-azure-vm/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer:
I created this document based on an open source contribution to Airbyte. Please refer to the source document at Deploy on Azure   This page guides you through deploying Airbyte Open Source on a Microsoft Azure VM by setting up the deployment environment, installing and starting Airbyte, and connecting it to the VM.
Note:
The instructions have been tested on a standard DS1 v2 (1 vcpu, 3.5 GiB memory) Microsoft Azure VM with Ubuntu 18.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Are Two Key Differences Between BigQuery and Redshift?</title>
      <link>https://sblaizerwize.github.io/posts/bigqueryvsredshift/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sblaizerwize.github.io/posts/bigqueryvsredshift/</guid>
      <description>Big Data. We often hear about this word but we aren’t quite sure how to define it. Literature says that having more than 1 TB of data can be considered as Big Data. After getting a mild idea of the concept, our next question would be: How can we manage such a large amount of data to find useful insights out of it? Well, one approach that can answer this lies in data warehousing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Create Python Packages</title>
      <link>https://sblaizerwize.github.io/posts/pythonpackages/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sblaizerwize.github.io/posts/pythonpackages/</guid>
      <description>A Python package is a collection of modules. A module is the easiest way to import and reuse existing Python code that’s developed by other programmers. In simple terms, a package is a module, but not all modules are packages. So, the question that raises is: what differentiates a package from a module? The response lies in a file named __init__.py, which indicates that the folder directory is a package. In this article, we’ll walk you through the main concepts and steps about how to create, install, publish, and test your own Python package locally and globally.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>